these are my notes from sitting here and
just thinking last night
they aren't clean they're not beautiful
I wouldn't expect anyone else to
understand them but it's how I work I
don't know how to edit video yet once I
figure that out I'm not even really
trying to figure it out yet but I do
have a longer video that I would like to
edit down that I think I do a fairly
good job of explaining in my cooperative
it in so that is a goal but in this
meantime I'm still doing my daily videos
and since this came up I'm going to talk
about it and that is with these notes
what I would have needed to be or what I
need to be to get any of my ideas into
the world and so I have the first part
which is that you have to have an idea
or or figure out what the problem is and
a solution and I've been doing that for
two decades figuring out the problems
and then sometimes solutions sometimes
not and figured all the introductive
connected problems and now I have this
idea this global cooperative which is
not it's complex and intervene just like
the problems that it solves and so I
have this idea that parts done the idea
part is done and now I have to be the
person or someone has to be the person
who explains it that kind of has to be
me app to be able to explain it at least
to a person who can then explain it I
feel to market it and get that idea out
to more people and expand it so that
they understand what is for trying to do
I have to create create it so it's an
idea for a lot of technology I'll be
able to code and do do those things
someone has to be able to I know I'm not
going to be that person
once it's created has someone has to be
able to maintain it which is a lot of
expertise right it's having the
financial expertise to know whether
you're the legal expertise know if
you're following the law the financial
is to know the taxes and how to make
money at it so that it's sustainable not
necessarily for profit but for just a
sustained to pay salaries pay people to
code to pay people do those things as
well as it when you're paying people to
have the HR department write it like you
need those expertise and when you start
a business or you start a project you're
ever
thing you also need to be able to to
improve it if you want further ideas you
want it to grow and so the research and
development departments as well as
recruitment so being able to have the
interpersonal skills to network and give
people again to explain it so that they
want to come on board so that people who
that would resonate with Ken and I
totally own I've done the first part and
I'm not good at the other parts and in
the capitalist system that just means
that came my idea sits on a shelf it
never gets made and that would be fine
if it was just a better mousetrap that
would be fine if it was just like a
slightly cooler looking car but this
idea is gonna save the world
and so I have to work from where I'm at
and the whole point of me struggling
with all of this and I'm struggling I'm
struggling to get this stuff out there
to figure out how to make videos to just
put myself on video and put myself on
YouTube and figure out how to explain it
the best is it best explained and
writing in a blog can I do it like
fantasy like it's already happened can I
do it in these videos when I don't even
know how to edit a video and but I'm
working for where I'm at and I want to
create a system everything I've
struggled with my health my
relationships are here so that when I
figure them out and I figure out
technology that helps and other people
who have struggled with those things
figure it out we can come together and
create systems so less people struggle I
want a system so that everyone's able to
give their unique gifts to the world
I truly believe we're not in competition
with each other every human being is
here for a unique purpose and to honor
that I do think that we need to have a
system that allows people to contribute
in a way that calls to them without
needing to be everything that you don't
need to be a marketer you don't need to
be the research and development person
or you cannot have like you don't need
to be the person who comes up with the
idea when you hear an idea and you can
give that message to somebody else what
an amazing gift to be able to be a
marketer I mean II support
word is very tied to capitalism and that
economy but that skill the skill to tell
the story and to explain what it is that
a product does and gives you in a real
authentic trustworthy way where it's not
hype and it's not you know selling it
with through through sex or it's just
explaining it what an amazing gift I
don't have that gift and so until
someone comes on board with that gift I
am stuck with me and doing all of these
things and so I just love it I love this
whole process where all of my like
stopping points and sticking points are
exactly where I need to be but it's
frustrating because I also want this out
in the world I want people to
collaborate with I want you know like
it's scary
I want Pete I want my videos to go viral
and I also really don't like that's
terrifying to be especially when we
don't switch one it might be or I'm so
already at five minutes but that is day
13 thank you